<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reeve Lorena</title>
    <link>https://reeve24.github.io/reeve.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Reeve Lorena</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://reeve24.github.io/reeve.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Choosing a Broker</title>
      <link>https://reeve24.github.io/reeve.github.io/posts/choosing_a_broker/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 10:45:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reeve24.github.io/reeve.github.io/posts/choosing_a_broker/</guid>
      <description>The first step that we have to take is to choose three brokers in order answer our research question.
The main requirement for this project is that the broker that we are using is open source. This is crucial as we would like to analyse the code to gain a deeper understanding of the broker in question.
These are the brokers that I am planning to analyse for the purpose of this project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Meeting</title>
      <link>https://reeve24.github.io/reeve.github.io/posts/first_meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reeve24.github.io/reeve.github.io/posts/first_meeting/</guid>
      <description>During my first meeting with Prof. AK Trivedi, we acknowledged that due to the Covid-19 pandemic and the quarantine situation in the Netherlands and also the lack of time on our hands, we decided that we would have to change our course of action slightly to ensure that I can deliver a quality final product in a timely fashion. We thus decided to shift our focus to comparing and analysing the various MQTT brokers currently in use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://reeve24.github.io/reeve.github.io/about-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reeve24.github.io/reeve.github.io/about-hugo/</guid>
      <description>This space shall be used to show my progress throughout my Thesis journey. You can follow my Thesis progress in the Posts section of this blog.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>